Piotr Karszny

Contact

Email: piotr.karszny@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/piotrkarszny

Profile

An experienced PHP developer, and currently a Go enthusiast. Immense Linux fan.

Embraces transparency, and communication as a significant aspect of the teamwork. Always wiling to help, and leverages knowledge sharing as a driver for constant improvement of his abilities.

Employment

Nexi Digital / software engineer

03.2023 - NOW

Stack: PHP, Azure, Docker, K8s

Boxdrop / software engineer

07.2021 - 02.2023

Stack: PHP, GO, Docker, JS, MariaDB

STS Gaming Group / software engineer

01.2021 - 06.2021

Tech stack: PHP, JS, MySQL, Docker

Boldare / software engineer

04.2014 - 12.2020

Tech stack: PHP, JS, MySQL, Docker, Vagrant

Studio-IT — server infrastructure administrator

02.2011 - 03.2014

Maintained LINUX/WINDOWS infrastructure (web servers, e-mail, databases)

Skills

Programming Languages PHP, GO, JavaScript, TypeScript

Database MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Infrastructure Docker, Vagrant, Ansible

Cloud AWS, RDS, EC2, S3, DynamoDB

CI/CD Travis, GitLab-CI, GitHub Actions

Version Control Git, GitHub, GitLab, BitBucket

Project/Team Management Agile, Scrum

Education

University of Humanities and Economics in Łódź — engineer's degree 2003-2007 - computer science, computer networks